Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
かわいいね
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいじゃん
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Aren't you an idol or something?
なんかアイドルとかやってないの?
No, not at all.
いやいや、全然そんなそんな
Yeah?
うん?
lie?
嘘?
Is it really cute?
めっちゃかわいい?
It's kind of embarrassing.
なんか恥ずかしいですね
Anma.
あんま
It's never been photographed here.
ここに撮られたことないもんね
that's right.
そうです
How old are you now?
今何歳なの?
I'm 10 years old now.
今10歳です
male?
男?
picture?
え?
What year is it?
何年ですよ?
I'm 10 years old here.
ここは10歳です
Man, is it fun?
男、楽しい?
Fair enough.
まあまあ
So-so?
まあまあ?
What do you enjoy?
何 が楽しい?
Like playing with friends.
友達と遊んだりとか
I'm going to enjoy it.
楽 しんできます
Is this how you do it?
こうやってやってんの?
I have hair that looks like it's going to grow back.
僕は 一応、生えそうな髪を
To.
へ ー
What are you doing?
何やってんの?
what?
何?
Kakko
か っこ
good.
いい
To.
へ ー
cool.
かっこいい
thank you.
ありがとうございます
If you have expectations.
期待があれば
Is it okay to have a cultural festival?
文化祭っていい?
Well then.
じゃあ
I'm going to go with this double-sided one, but is it okay?
この 複面のまま行くけど、 大丈夫なの?
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いんの?
It's been a long time now.
今は長いです
Ah, there it is.
あ、いるんだ
that's right.
そうです
Just in case.
一応
classmate?
同級生?
no.
いや
How long have you been together?
付き合ってどんくらいの?
We've been dating for about a year.
付き合って1年くらい
It's long.
長いね
That's right.
そうですよね
Did you confess?
告白したの?
That's what I was told.
言われたんだ
Are you going on a date?
デートとか行くの?
I'm going.
行きます
Where are you going?
どこ行くの?
Go to sightseeing spots and eat delicious food.
観光地に行ったり、 美味しいもの食べたり
Please eat.
食べてね
Did you have sex?
エッチした?
I had sex.
エッチした
I did.
しました
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいいの?
When was the first time?
初めてしたのはいつなの?
After entering?
入ってから?
Who did you do it with?
誰としたの?
this is
これは
...
boyfriend?
彼 氏?
Eh, what do you mean?
え、どういうこと?
Were you dating your teacher?
先生と付き合ってたの?
Which teacher?
どの先生?
Are you a teacher at your current school?
今の学校の先生ってこと?
picture?
え?
Is there such a thing?
そんなことある?
Top secret.
トップシークレットで
Why did you end up in such a relationship?
なんでそんな関係になっちゃったの?
picture?
え?
This is the second one.
2つ目です
How old are you, teacher?
先生何歳?
My teacher forced me to do it.
先生に無理やりやられちゃったんだよ
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
Did you like it?
好きだった?
Should I become a teacher?
先生になろうかな?
Study.
勉強して
You can have such a cute girlfriend, right?
こんな可愛い彼女できるでしょ?
that's right.
そうです
How did you know?
なんで分かっちゃったの?
Isn't it too late to notice?
気づくの遅くない?
Not the first thing you think?
最初に思わない?
Well, that may be the case.
まあ、そういうこともあります
What was it like the first time?
初めてしたときはどうだったの?
I was nervous.
緊張してたんだ
Did it hurt?
痛かったりした?
I'm starting to fall in love with you.
好きになりかけてる俺は
So cute.
可愛いな
Why are you so cute?
なんでそんな可愛いの?
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してますね
Do you agree with your boyfriend a lot?
彼氏と一致いっぱいしてんの?
No, not that much at all.
いや、全然そんなに
picture?
え?
so?
そんなに?
it is?
それは?
Those are beautiful feet.
綺麗な足だね
It's very thin.
すごく細いね
I just had a nosebleed.
さっき鼻血出ちゃったよ
You saw it, right?
見たよね?
Are you giving your boyfriend a nosebleed?
彼氏に鼻血出させるの?
That's not true.
そんなことないですよ
TRUE?
本当?
Are you nervous?
緊張してるでしょ?
The one that isn't included
入ってないやつ
mosquito.
か
Wow, your skin is beautiful.
すごい 肌綺麗だね
It's white.
白いね
There are scary people.
怖い人がいる
It's a shame that you did this.
これやらし惜しいしてるね
copper?
どう?
That's naughty.
やらしい
Miss.
お嬢さん
I sat down once.
一 回座ったよ
Doesn't the young lady take off her shirt every time?
お嬢さんの毎シャツ脱いでしょ?
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗だね
terrible.
やばい